<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--String related to help activity-->
    <string name="question1">How to start the cycling trip?</string>
    <string name="answer1">You can tap on the cycling icon to start the trip.
        When you start the trip you can see you distance travelled,time and speed. </string>
    <string name="question2">Are my cycling trip details stored somewhere?</string>
    <string name="answer2">Your cycling trip details are not stored if you are not logged in. Once you register and login your details
        get stored in the our database and you can also see the details of your previous trips by clicking on history.</string>
    <string name="question3">How do I abort a trip?</string>
    <string name="answer3">You can cancel or abort a trip by clicking on the grey cancel button which is at the bottom in cycling page. If you abort/cancel
    a trip the details of that trip will not be stored in the database even if you are logged in.</string>
    <string name="question4">How do I stop a trip? </string>
    <string name="answer4">You can stop a trip by clicking on the round stop button. The details of the stopped trips will be saved in the database if you are logged in</string>
    <string name="question5">How do I register?
    </string>
    <string name="answer5">Goto the register page enter your name, valid mobile and password and click on register. You will then be redirected to the
    OTP verification page.On that page enter the 4 digit number that will be sent to your mobile number and click on verify.
        If you have correctly done all the above you will be registered and logged in.</string>
    <string name="question6">What does the summary page show me?</string>
    <string name="answer6">When you stop a cycling trip your are redirected to summary page on which you can see the total distance that you travelled during that trip
    the time taken in that trip and the average speed in that trip.</string>
</resources>